Finding Aid for College of Literature, Science and the Arts (University of Michigan) records, 1846-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean’s Files 1916-2008
  - 2002-2003
    - Centers/Institutes/Museums/Programs
      - American Culture (Box 481)
      - Applied Physics (Box 481)
      - Armenian Studies (Box 481)
      - Atlantic Studies Program (Box 481)
      - Biological Station (Box 481)
      - Botanical Gardens (Matthaei) (Box 481)
      - Chinese Studies, Center for (CCS) (Box 481)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology (Box 481)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 481)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP) (Box 481)
      - Computer Science Program (Box 481)
      - English Language Institute (ELI) (Box 481)
      - Environment, Program in the (PITE) (Box 481)
      - European Studies (Box 481)
      - Exhibit Museum (Box 481)
      - Film and Video Studies
        - General (Box 481)
        - External Director Search (Box 474)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2033 ]
      - Great Lakes and Aquatic Sciences, center for (CGLAS) (Box 481)
      - Greek and Roman History, Interdepartmental Program in (Box 481)
      - Health Sciences Scholars Program (HSSP) (Box 481)
      - Herbarium (Box 481)
      - Honors Program (Box 482)
      - Humanities, Institute for the
        - General (Box 482)
        - External Review (Box 482)
      - International Institute (Box 482)
      - International Programs, Office of (OIP) (Box 482)
      - Japanese Studies (note: includes materials on external review) (Box 482)
      - Judaic Studies
        - General (Box 482)
        - External Review (Box 482)
      - Korean Studies (Box 482)
      - Language Resource Center (LRC) (Box 482)
      - Latin American and Caribbean Studies (Box 482)
      - Lloyd Hall Scholars Program (LHSP) (Box 482)
      - Medieval/Early Modern Studies (MEMS) (Box 482)
      - Michigan Community Scholars Program (MCSP) (Box 482)
      - Middle Eastern and North African Studies (Box 482)
      - Museum of Anthropology (Box 482)
      - Museum of Archaeology (Box 482)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 482)
      - Museum Studies Program (Box 482)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 482)
      - Museums: General (Box 482)
      - Organizational Studies Program (Box 482)
      - Religion, Studies in (Box 482)
      - Residential College (RC) (Box 482)
      - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (CREES) (Box 483)
      - Scandinavian Studies (Box 483)
      - Science Learning Center (SLC) (Box 483)
      - Science, Technology and Society (STS) (Box 483)
      - Sikh Studies (Box 483)
      - South Asian Studies (Box 483)
      - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP) (Box 483)
      - Women's Studies (Box 483)
      - Writing Center, Sweetland (SWC) (Box 483)
  - 2003-2004
    - Topical Files
      - A, General (Box 483)
        [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2030 ]
      - Academic Program Group (APG)
        - General (Box 483)
        - Development Subcommittee (Box 483)
      - Admissions and Admissions Committees
        - General, 2 folders (Box 483)
        - Student Information (Box 491)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2079 ]
      - ADVANCE Project, 3 folders (Box 483)
      - Art, Museum of (UMMA) (Box 483)
      - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 483)
      - Awards and Fellowships
        - General (Box 483)
        - Congrats Letters (Box 483)
      - Budget, 3 folders (Box 484)
      - Business School (Box 484)
      - C, General (Box 484)
      - Chairs and Directors
        - Letters, 2 folders (Box 484)
        - Meetings, 2 folders (Box 484)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) (Box 484)
      - Complex Systems, Program for the Study of (Box 484)
      - Condolence Letters (Box 484)
      - Curriculum (Box 484)
      - D, General (Box 484)
      - Dean's Advisory Council (Box 484)
      - Deans Meeting (LSA) (Box 484)
      - Dean's Office Reorganization: Associate Deans (Box 484)
      - Dean's Office Reorganization: Budget (Box 484)
      - Development -- LSA, 2 folders (Box 485)
      - Development -- University (Box 485)
      - E. General (Box 485)
      - Education, School of (Box 485)
      - Elections (Box 485)
      - Engineering, School of (Box 485)
      - Enrollments (Box 485)
      - Executive Committee (Box 485)
      - F, General (Box 491)
      - Facilities (Space) (Box 485)
      - Faculty (Box 485)
      - Faculty Meetings (Box 485)
      - Faculty Reception (Box 485)
      - Faculty Recruitment and Retention (Box 485)
      - Festival of New Works (Box 485)
      - Financial Aid (Box 485)
      - First Year Seminars (Box 485)
      - Flexible Tenure (Box 485)
      - Ford Nuclear Reactor (Box 485)
      - Foreign Language (Box 485)
      - Funding Requests, 2 folders (Box 485)
      - G, General (Box 485)
      - Gender Institute (Box 485)
      - Grading (Box 485)
      - Graduate Employee Organization (GEO) (Box 485)
      - Graduate Student Instructors (GSI's) (Box 485)
      - Graduate Student Research Assistants (GSRA's) (Box 485)
      - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of (Box 485)
      - Graduation (Box 485)
      - Grievance Procedure (Box 485)
      - H, General (Box 485)
      - Holidays (Box 485)
      - I, General (Box 486)
      - Imagining America (Box 486)
      - Information Technology: LSA (Box 486)
      - Information Technology: University (Box 486)
      - Intergroup Relations and Conflict Project (Box 486)
      - J, General (Box 486)
      - K, General (Box 486)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day (Box 486)
      - L, General (Box 486)
      - Lecturers (Box 486)
      - Libraries (University) (Box 486)
      - Life Sciences Institute (Box 486)
      - Life Sciences Undergraduate Initiative (Box 486)
      - LSA Magazine (Box 486)
      - M, General
        - General (Box 486)
        - Student Information (Box 491)
      - Medical School (Box 486)
      - Mellon Foundation (Box 486)
      - Memorials (Box 486)
      - M-Pathways (Box 486)
      - N, General (Box 486)
      - Nano Science and Engineering Initiative (Box 486)
      - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 486)
      - Natural Resources and Environment, School of (SNRE) (Box 486)
      - Neuroscience (Box 486)
      - Nominating Committee (Box 486)
      - O, General (Box 486)
      - Ombudsman (Box 486)
      - Position Requests (Box 486)
      - President (Box 486)
      - Primary Research Scientists (Box 486)
      - Promotions (Box 486)
      - Provost (Box 486)
      - Public Policy, School of (Box 486)
      - R, General (Box 486)
      - Rankings (Box 486)
      - Research and Graduate Studies, Associate Dean for (Box 486)
      - Research on Learning and Teaching, Center for (CRLT) (Box 486)
      - Research, Vice President for (OVPR) (Box 486)
      - Retirements (Box 486)
      - S, General (Box 487)
      - Scholarships (Box 487)
      - Senior Lecturers (Box 487)
      - Senior Professor Lecture (Box 487)
      - Sexual Harassment
        - General (Box 487)
        - Personnel Information (Box 491)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2034 ]
      - Social Research, Institute for (Box 487)
      - Student Academic Affairs, Office of (Box 487)
      - Student Affairs, Vice President for (Box 487)
      - Student Government (Box 487)
      - Student Recruitment (Box 487)
      - Students
        - General (Box 487)
        - Student Information (Box 491)
      - T, General (Box 487)
      - Tenure (Box 487)
      - Theme Semesters (Box 487)
      - U, General (Box 487)
      - Undergraduate Education (Box 487)
      - V, General (Box 487)
      - W, General (Box 487)
    - Departments
      - Anthropology
        - General, 2 folders (Box 487)
        - Personnel Information (Box 491)
      - Asian Language and Cultures, 2 folders (Box 491)
      - Astronomy
        - General (Box 487)
        - Student Information (Box 491)
      - Chemistry
        - General, 2 folders (Box 487)
        - Personnel Information (Box 491)
        - Student Information (Box 491)
      - Classical Studies (Box 487)
      - Communication Studies
        - General (Box 487)
        - External Review (Box 487)
      - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology (Box 487)
      - Economics (Box 488)
        - General (Box 488)
        - Student Information (Box 491)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2079 ]
      - English
        - General, 2 folders (Box 488)
        - David Halperin -- Gay Studies Class (includes audiotape of March 31, 2000 Interview on WJR re: Eng. 317: "How To Be Gay") (Box 488)
      - Geological Sciences
        - General (Box 488)
        - Personnel Information (Box 491)
      - German (Box 488)
      - History
        - General (Box 488)
        - External Review (Box 488)
      - History of Art (Box 488)
      - Linguistics (Box 488)
      - Mathematics
        - General (Box 488)
        - Student Information (Box 491)
      - Molecular, Cellular, and Developmental Biology (Box 488)
      - Near Eastern Studies
        - General (Box 488)
        - Personnel Information (Box 491)
      - Philosophy (Box 488)
      - Physics
        - General, 3 folders (Box 488)
        - Michigan Center for Theoretical Physics (Box 488)
      - Political Science (Box 489)
      - Psychology (Box 489)
      - Romance Language (Box 489)
      - Slavic Languages (Box 489)
      - Sociology
        - General (Box 489)
        - Detroit Area Study (Box 489)
        - Personnel Information (Box 491)
      - Statistics (Box 489)
    - Centers/Institutes/Museums/Programs
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (CAAS) (Box 489)
      - American Culture (Box 489)
      - Anthropology -- History Interdepartmental Program (Box 489)
      - Applied Physics (Box 489)
      - Armenian Studies (Box 489)
      - Atlantic Studies (Box 489)
      - Biological Station (Box 489)
      - Botanical Gardens (Matthaei) (Box 489)
      - Chinese Studies, Center for (CCS) (Box 489)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology (Box 489)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 489)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP) (Box 490)
      - Computer Science Program (Box 490)
      - English Language Institute (ELI) (Box 490)
      - Environment, Program in the (PITE) (Box 490)
      - European Studies (Box 490)
      - Exhibit Museum (Box 490)
      - Film and Video Studies
        - General (Box 490)
        - External Review (Box 490)
      - Great Books Program (Box 490)
      - Greek and Roman History, Interdepartmental Program in (Box 490)
      - Herbarium
        - General (Box 490)
        - Herbarium and Museum of Zoology Director Search (Box 490)
      - Honors Program (Box 490)
      - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 490)
      - International Institute (Box 490)
      - International Programs, Office of (OIP) (Box 490)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 490)
      - Korean Studies (Box 490)
      - Language Resource Center (LRC) (Box 490)
      - Latin American and Caribbean Studies (Box 490)
      - Lloyd Hall Scholars Program (LHSP) (Box 490)
      - Medieval/Early Modern Studies (MEMS) (Box 490)
      - Michigan Community Scholars Program (MCSP) (Box 490)
      - Middle Eastern and North African Studies (Box 490)
      - Museum of Anthropology, 2 folders (Box 490)
      - Museum of Archaeology (Box 490)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 490)
      - Museum Studies Program (Box 490)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 490)
      - Organizational Studies Program (Box 490)
      - Religion, Program on Studies in (PSIR) (Box 490)
      - Residential College (Box 490)
      - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (CREES) (Box 490)
      - Sikh Studies (Box 490)
      - South Asian Studies (Box 490)
      - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP) (Box 490)
      - Women's Studies (Box 490)
      - Writing Center, Sweetland (SWC) (Box 490)
  - 2004-2005
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 492)
        [ER RESTRICTED until July 17, 2032 ]
      - Asian Language and Cultures (Box 492)
      - Astronomy (Box 492)
      - Chemistry, 3 folders (Box 491)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2035 ]
      - Classical Studies (Box 492)
      - Communication Studies (Box 492)
      - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology (EEB) (Box 492)
      - Economics (Box 492)
      - English (Box 492)
      - Geological Sciences (Box 492)
      - German (Box 492)
      - History (Box 492)
      - History of Art (Box 492)
      - Linguistics (Box 492)
      - Mathematics (Box 492)
      - Molecular, Cellular, and Developmental Biology (Box 492)
      - Near Eastern Studies (Box 492)
      - Philosophy (Box 492)
      - Physics, 2 folders (Box 492)
      - Physics: Michigan Center for Theoretical Physics (Box 492)
      - Political Science (Box 492)
      - Psychology (Box 492)
      - Romance Languages Slavic Languages (Box 493)
      - Sociology (Box 493)
      - Statistics (Box 493)
    - Centers/Institutes/Museums/Programs
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (CAAS) (Box 493)
      - American Culture (Box 493)
      - Applied Physics (Box 493)
      - Armenian Studies (Box 493)
      - Atlantic Studies (Box 493)
      - Biological Station (Box 493)
      - Chinese Studies, Center for (CCS) (Box 493)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology (Box 493)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 493)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP) (Box 493)
      - Computer Science Program (Box 493)
      - English Language Institute (ELI) (Box 493)
      - Environment, Program in the (PITE) (Box 493)
      - European Studies (Box 493)
      - Exhibit Museum (Box 493)
      - Film and Video Studies (Box 493)
      - Greek and Roman History (Box 493)
      - Herbarium (Box 493)
      - Honors Program (Box 493)
      - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 493)
      - IDEA Institute (Box 493)
      - International Institute (Box 493)
      - International Programs, Office of (OIP) (Box 493)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 493)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 493)
      - Korean Studies (Box 493)
      - Language Resource Center (LRC) (Box 493)
      - Lloyd Hall Scholars Program (LHSP) (Box 493)
      - Medieval/Early Modern Studies (MEMS) (Box 493)
      - Michigan Community Scholars Program (MCSP) (Box 493)
      - Modern Greek Studies (Box 493)
      - Museum of Anthropology, 2 folders (Box 494)
      - Museum of Archaeology (Box 494)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 494)
      - Museum Studies Program (Box 494)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 494)
      - Organizational Studies Program (Box 494)
      - Residential College (Box 494)
      - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (CREES) (Box 494)
      - Sikh Studies (Box 494)
      - South Asian Studies (Box 494)
      - Southeast Asian Studies (Box 494)
      - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP) (Box 494)
      - Women's Studies (Box 494)
      - Writing Center, Sweetland (SWC) (Box 494)
    - Topical Files
      - A, General (Box 494)
      - Academic Program Group (APG), 2 folders (Box 494)
      - APG Development Subcommittee (Box 494)
      - Admissions and Admissions Committees (Box 494)
      - ADVANCE Project, 3 folders (Box 494)
      - Art, Museum of (UMMA) (Box 494)
      - Art, School of (Box 494)
      - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 495)
      - Awards: Congratulatory Letters (Box 495)
      - Awards and Fellowships: General (Box 495)
      - B, General (Box 495)
      - Budget, 2 folders (Box 495)
      - Business School (Box 495)
      - C, General (Box 495)
      - Chairs and Directors
        - Letters to (Box 495)
        - Meetings, 5 folders (Box 495)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) (Box 495)
      - Complex Systems, Program for the Study of (Box 495)
      - Condolence Letters (Box 495)
      - Curriculum (Box 495)
      - D, General (Box 495)
      - Dean's Advisory Council, 2 folders (Box 495)
      - Dean's Meeting: (LSA) (Box 495)
      - Development -- LSA, 2 folders (Box 496)
      - Development -- University (Box 496)
      - Divisional Associate Deans (Box 496)
      - Education, School of
        - School of Education Dean's Search Committee; May 2004-June 2005 (Box 496)
      - Elections (Box 496)
      - Engineering, College of, 2 folders (Box 496)
      - Enrollments (Box 496)
      - Executive Committee (Box 496)
      - F, General (Box 496)
      - Facilities (Space) (Box 496)
      - Faculty (Box 496)
      - Faculty Meetings (Box 496)
      - Faculty Reception (Box 496)
      - Faculty Recruitment and Retention
      - First-Year Seminars
      - Flexible Tenure, 2 folders (Box 496)
      - Ford Motor Company (Box 496)
      - Foreign Language (Box 496)
      - Funding Requests (Box 496)
      - G, General (Box 496)
      - Gender Institute (Box 496)
      - Graduate Employees Organization (GEO) (Box 496)
      - Graduate Student Instructors (GSI) (Box 496)
      - Graduate Studies, Rackham School of (Box 497)
      - Graduation (Box 497)
      - Grievance Procedure (Box 497)
      - H, General (Box 497)
      - Holidays (Box 497)
      - I, General (Box 497)
      - Information Technology: LSA (Box 497)
      - Intergroup Relations and Conflict Project (Box 497)
      - J, General (Box 497)
      - K, General (Box 497)
      - Key Administrators (Box 497)
      - L, General (Box 497)
      - Lecturers -- Employee Organization (LEO) (Box 497)
      - Libraries (University) (Box 497)
      - Life Sciences Institute, 2 folders (Box 497)
      - Life Sciences Undergraduate Initiative (Box 497)
      - Living-Learning Programs (Box 497)
      - M, General (Box 497)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day (Box 497)
      - Medical School (Box 497)
      - Memorials (Box 497)
      - M-Pathways (Box 497)
      - N, General (Box 497)
      - National Science and Engineering Initiative (Box 497)
      - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 497)
      - Neuroscience (Box 497)
      - Nominating Committee (Box 497)
      - O, General (Box 497)
      - Ombudsman (Box 497)
      - P, General (Box 497)
      - P, General (Box 497)
      - Position Requests, 2 folders (Box 497)
      - President (Box 497)
      - Promotions (Box 497)
      - Provost (Box 497)
      - Public Policy, School of (Box 497)
      - Rankings (Box 497)
      - Research: LSA (Box 497)
      - Research on Learning and Teaching, Center for (CRLT) (Box 497)
      - Research, Vice President for (OVPR) (Box 497)
      - Retirements (Box 498)
      - S, General (Box 498)
      - Scholarships (Box 498)
      - Senate Assembly/SACUA (Box 498)
      - Senior Lecturers (Box 498)
      - Senior (Distinguished) Professor Lecture (Box 498)
      - Sexual Harassment (Box 498)
      - Social Research, Institute for (Box 498)
      - Student Academic Affairs, Office of (Box 498)
      - Student Affairs, Vice President for (Box 498)
      - Students: General (Box 498)
      - Student Government (LSA) (Box 498)
      - T, General (Box 498)
      - Tenure (Box 498)
      - Theme Semesters (Box 498)
      - Undergraduate & Graduate Education, Associate Dean (Box 498)
      - W, General (Box 498)
  - 2005-2006
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 498)
      - Asian Languages (Box 498)
      - Astronomy (Box 498)
      - Magellan Project (Box 498)
      - Chemistry (Box 498)
      - Classical Studies (Box 498)
      - Communication Studies (Box 498)
      - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology (EEB) (Box 498)
      - Economics (Box 498)
      - English (Box 498)
      - Geological Sciences (Box 498)
      - German (Box 498)
      - History (Box 498)
      - History of Art (Box 498)
      - Linguistics (Box 498)
      - Mathematics (Box 498)
      - Molecular, Cellular, and Developmental Biology (Box 498)
      - Near Eastern Studies (Box 498)
      - Philosophy (Box 498)
      - Physics (Box 498)
      - Physics: Michigan Center for Theoretical Physics (Box 499)
      - Political Science (Box 499)
      - Psychology (Box 499)
      - Romance Languages (Box 499)
      - Screen Arts and Cultures (Box 499)
      - Slavic Languages (Box 499)
      - Sociology (Box 499)
      - Statistics (Box 499)
      - Women's Studies (Box 499)
    - Centers/Institutes/Museums/Programs
      - Center/Institute/Program: General (Box 499)
      - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (CAAS) (Box 499)
      - American Culture (Box 499)
      - Applied Physics (Box 499)
      - Armenian Studies (Box 499)
      - Biological Station (Box 499)
      - Biophysics Research (Box 499)
      - Chinese Studies (Box 499)
      - Classical Art and Archaeology (IPCAA) (Box 499)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 499)
      - Comprehensive Studies Program (CSP) (Box 499)
      - English Language Institute (ELI) (includes CD-ROM) (Box 499)
      - Environment, Program in the (PITE) (Box 499)
      - European Studies (Box 499)
      - Exhibit Museum (Box 499)
      - Greek and Roman History (Box 499)
      - Herbarium (Box 499)
      - Historical Studies, Institute for (Box 499)
      - Honors Program (Box 499)
      - Humanities, Institute for the (Box 499)
      - IDEA Institute (Box 499)
      - International Institute (Box 499)
      - International and Comparative Studies, Center for (Box 499)
      - International Programs, Office of (OIP) (Box 499)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 499)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 499)
      - Korean Studies (Box 499)
      - Lloyd Hall Scholars Program (LHSP) (Box 499)
      - Medieval/Early Modern Studies (MEMS) (Box 499)
      - Michigan Community Scholars Program (MCSP) (Box 499)
      - Middle Eastern and North African Studies (Box 499)
      - Museum of Anthropology (Box 499)
      - Museum of Archaeology (Box 499)
      - Museum of Paleontology (Box 499)
      - Museum Studies Program (Box 499)
      - Museum of Zoology (Box 499)
      - Organizational Studies Program (Box 499)
      - Peking University Joint Institute (Box 500)
      - Residential College (Box 500)
      - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (CREES) (Box 500)
      - Science, Technology & Society (Box 500)
      - Sikh Studies (Box 500)
      - South Asian Studies (Box 500)
      - Southeast Asian Studies (Box 500)
      - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program (UROP) (Box 500)
      - Weiser Center for Europe & Eurasia (Box 500)
      - Writing Center, Sweetland (SWC) (Box 500)
    - Topical Files
      - A, General (Box 500)
      - Academic Program Group (APG) (Box 500)
      - APG Development Subcommittee (Box 500)
      - Admissions and Admissions Committees (Box 500)
      - ADVANCE Project, 2 folders (Box 500)
      - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 500)
      - Awards: Congratulatory Letters (Box 500)
      - Awards and Fellowships: General (Box 500)
      - B, General (Box 500)
      - Budget, 3 folders (Box 500)
      - Business School (Box 500)
      - C, General (Box 500)
      - Chairs and Directors
        - Letters to (Box 500)
        - Meetings (1 -- 4 of 5 folders) (Box 500)
        - Meetings (folder 5 of 5) (Box 501)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) (Box 501)
      - Condolence Letters (Box 501)
      - Curriculum (Box 501)
      - D, General (Box 501)
      - Dean's Advisory Council (Box 501)
      - Dean's Meeting: (LSA) (Box 501)
      - Development -- LSA (Box 501)
        (includes CD-ROM)
      - Development -- University (Box 501)
      - Divisional Associate Deans (Box 501)
      - E, General (Box 501)
      - Education, School of (Box 501)
      - Elections (Box 501)
      - Engineering, College of (Box 501)
      - Enrollments (Box 501)
      - Executive Committee (Box 501)
      - F, General (Box 501)
      - Facilities (Space) (Box 501)
      - Faculty (Box 501)
      - Faculty Code (Box 501)
      - Faculty Meetings (Box 501)
      - Faculty Reception (Box 501)
      - Faculty Recruitment and Retention
      - Financial Aid